Guide to the Records of the Office of Research Services/Office of Sponsored Programs RG.9.4
New York University Archives
- University Administration, 88247
  - Deputy Chancellor, Office of, 1995-1996; 88262 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Research Administration, 88263
  - The World War II Era, 1940-1946; 88264 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Organized Research, 1949-1952; 88265 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Research Services, Office of, 1952-1959; 88266 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Research Services, Office of, 1960-1969; 88267 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Research Services/Sponsored Programs, Office of (name change 1971), 1970-1977; 88268 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, 1978-1979; 88269 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, 1980; 88270 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, 1981-1985; 88271 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, 1985-1991; 88272 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, 1992-1993; 88273 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, 1994-1997; 88274 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Sponsored Progarms, Office of, Research Management Improvement (National Science Foundation Grant nm44242), 1974-1977; 88275 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Research Management Improvment (National Science Foundation Grant nm44242), 1974-1977; 88276 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Research Management Imporvement (National Science Foundation Grant nm44242), 1974-1977; 88277 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Intramural memoranda and minutes, 1974-1977; 88278 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Intramural memoranda and minutes, 1974-1977; 88279 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Intramural memoranda and minutes, 1974-1977; 88280 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Extramural Correspondence, 1974-1983; 88281 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Budget, Estimates, misc, 1975-1980; 88282 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Compliments, 1978-1996; 88283 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Cooper & Lybrand Study, 1987; 88284 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Cornell/NSF Town Meeting, 1994; 88285 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Development of Data Analysis, 1983-1985; 88286 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Freedom of Information Requests, 1981-1990; 88287 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Sponsored Programs and Operations, General University Certifications, 1990-1997; 88288 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Guide to Service, n.d.; 88289 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Log, 1963-1964; 88290 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Log, 1964-1965; 88291 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Log, 1965-1966; 88292 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Log, 1966-1967; 88293 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations Manuals, misc, 1958-1959; 88294 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Memoranda & Correspondence, 1959-1960; 88295 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Memoranda, & Correspondence, 1960; 88296 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Memoranda & Correspondence, 1961; 88297 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Memoranda & Correspondence, 1962-1965; 88298 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Sponsored Programs, Operations, Memoranda, & Operations, 1968-1971; 88299 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Memoranda, & Correspondence, 1971-1972; 88300 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Memoranda, & Correspondences, 1972-1974; 88301 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Memoranda, & Correspondence, 1974-1976; 88302 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, newsletters, 1979-1984; 88303 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, NYU Annual Report (Five year Retrospective), 1985-1987; 88304 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Program Announcements, 1972-1997; 88305 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Research Recognition Award Proposal, 1982; 88306 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Signature Authority, 1971-2005; 88307 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Staffing and Budgets, 1973-1989; 88308 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Senior Staff Activates, 1986-1997; 88309 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Senior Staff Activates meeting agendas and minutes, 1993-1997; 88310 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Sponsored Research and Training Programs Manual, 1956-1967; 88311 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Sponsored Research and Traning Programs Manual, 1973; 88312 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Sponsored Research and Training Programs Manual, 1974-1977; 88313 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Sponsored Research and Training Program Manual, 1978-1986; 88314 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Sponsored Research and Training Program Manual, 1991-1997; 88315 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Research Administration, Related University Units, 88346
  - Academic Affairs, Office of, 1982-1990; 88347 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs, Office of, Ethics and Moral Value, 1978-1982; 88348 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Services, Equipment and Policy and Property Management, 1979-1998; 88349 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Development Office, 1958-1968; 88350 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Development Office, 1975-1982; 88351 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Development Office, 1983; 88352 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Development Office, 1983-1985; 88353 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Development Office, 1985-1991; 88354 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Development Office, 1991-1993; 88355 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Development Office, 1994-1996; 88356 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1966-1981; 88357 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1981-1982; 88358 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1982-1983; 88359 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1983-1984; 88360 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1984-1986; 88361 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1986-1987; 88362 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1987-1988; 88363 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1988-1989; 88364 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1989-1990; 88365 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1990-1991; 88366 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1991-1992; 88367 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1992-1993; 88368 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1993-1994; 88369 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1994-1995; 88370 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1995-1996; 88371 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Finance Office, Indirect Cost Agreements, 1963-1995; 88372 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Finance Office, Indirect Cost Policy, Privately Sponsored Programs, 1985-1993; 88373 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Finance Office, Sponsored Research Accounting, 1974-1985; 88374 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Finance Office, Sponsored Research Accounting, 1986-1989; 88375 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Finance Office, Sponsored Research Accounting, 1989-1991; 88376 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Finance Office, Sponsored Research Accounting, 1991-1993; 88377 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Finance Office, Sponsored Research Accounting, 1993-1996; 88378 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Personnel Matters, Code 103, 1981-1996; 88382 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Personnel Matters, Tax Cases, 1958-1983; 88383 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Personnel Matters, Tax Cases, 1986-1988; 88384 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Schools/Units, 88379
  - Graduate School Arts and Science, 1957-1966; 88380 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School Arts and Science, 1967-1968; 88381 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Graduate School Arts and Science, 1968-1972; 88385 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, 1983; 88386 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, 1983-1986; 88387 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, 1986; 88388 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, 1986-1989; 88389 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, 1989-1990; 88390 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, 1993-1994; 88391 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, 1994-1998; 88392 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Deans' Correspondence and Memoranda, 1978-1991; 88393 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Dean of Science, 1989-1992; 88394 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Dean of Science, 1992-1995; 88395 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Neural Science, Center for, 1987-1988; 88396 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Neural Science, Center for, 1989; 88397 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, New York State Center for Neural Science at New York University, 1987-1989; 88398 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, New York State Center for Neural Science at New York University (1 of 2), 1989; 232778 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, New York State Center for Neural Science at New York University (2 of 2), 1989; 88399 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, New York State Center for Neural Science at New York University, 1989-1990; 88400 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Research Awards and Gifts, 1981-1983; 88401 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Technology Transfer Fund, 1990-1995; 88402 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Anthropology Department, 1968-1996; 88403 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Biology Department, 1959-1983; 88404 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Biology Department, Goldfeder Laboratory, 1973-1993; 88405 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Economics Department, 1969-1980; 88425 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Linguistics Department, 1982-1983; 88426 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Politics Department, 1983-1993; 88427 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Psychology Department (including Neural Science Center), 1980-1988; 88428 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Sociology Department, 1970-1993; 88429 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Applied Science, 1974-1989; 88430 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Applied Science, Kinetic Hydro Engergy Conversion Study, 1984-1988; 88431 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Westbury Facility, 1984-1989; 88432 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1961-1983; 88433 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Courant Insitute of Mathematical Sciences, 1983-1986; 88434 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1986-1997; 88435 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Center for Advanced Technology, 1982-1983; 88436 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1979-1997; 88437 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Continuing Education, School of, 1966-1968; 88438 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - College of Dentistry, 1968-1997; 88439 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - School of Education, 1959-1965; 88440 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - School of Education, 1965-1968; 88441 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - School of Education, 1968-1971; 88442 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - School of Education, 1979-1985; 88443 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - School of Education, 1985-1986; 88444 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - School of Education, 1986-1987; 88445 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - School of Education, 1987-1988; 88446 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - School of Education, 1988-1989; 88447 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - School of Education, 1989-1992; 88448 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - School of Education, 1992-1997; 88449 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - School of Engineering, 1965-1968; 88463 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - School of Engineering, 1969-1974; 88464 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - School of Law, 1988-1992; 88465 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - School of Medicine, Medical Center, 1962-1967; 88466 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - School of Medicine, Medical Center, 1968-1977; 88467 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - School of Medicine, Medical Center, 1982-1987; 88469 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - School of Medicine, Medical Center, 1987-1992; 88470 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - School of Medicine, Medical Center, 1992-1994; 88472 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - School of Medicine, Medical Center, 1994-1996; 88473 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1971-1992; 88474 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Graduate School of Social Work, 1967-1988; 88475 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Tisch School of the Arts, 1967-1982; 88476 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Center for International Studies, 1965; 88477 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Center for International Studies, 1966-1973; 88478 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Creative Arts Team, 1981-1985; 88479 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Creative Arts Team, 1986-1993; 88480 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Sponsor Matters, 88481
  - Classified/Confidential Work at Universities, 1966-1970; 88482 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Classified/Confidential Work at Universities, 1978-1980; 88483 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Classified/Confidential Work at Universities, 1985-1986; 88484 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Federal, Air Force Basic Agreement, 1960-1969; 88485 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Federal, Air Force Basic Agreement, 1970-1975; 88486 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Federal, Air Force Faculties Contract, Property Contract, 1961-1989; 88487 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Federal, Department of the Army, 1958-1967; 88488 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Federal, Department of the Navy Basic Agreement, 1969-1973; 88489 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Federal, Department of the Navy Basic Agreement, 1974-1986; 88490 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Federal, Department of the Navy Master Contract, 1961-1969; 88491 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Federal, DOD Critical Technologies Plan, Questionnaire, 1990; 88492 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Federal, DOD Strategic Defense Initiative, 1984-1985; 88493 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Federal, Atomic Energy Commission Basic Agreement, 1960-1966; 88494 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Federal, Atomic Energy Commission Basic Agreement, 1968; 88495 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Federal, Atomic Energy Commission Basic Agreement, 1969-1972; 88497 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Federal, Atomic Energy Commission, Misc, 1970-1972; 88498 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Federal, Department of Energy Basic Agreement, 1978-1979; 88499 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Federal, Department of Energy Basic Agreement, 1980-1987; 88500 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Federal, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1994-2000; 88501 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Federal, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Renovation and Extension of Guggenheim School of Aeronautics, 1963; 88502 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - State/City, AdHoc Committee on Relations with New York City, 1974-1975; 88503 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, 1985-1986; 88504 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, Board of Education, 1986; 88505 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, Board of Education, 1986-1987; 88506 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, Board of Education, 1987-1988; 88507 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, Board of Education, 1988; 88508 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, Board of Education, 1989; 88509 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, Board of Education, 1989; 88510 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, Board of Education, 1989-1994; 88511 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - State/City, New York State/City Default Committee, 1995-1996; 88512 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - State/City, New York State/City Funding, 1988-1991; 88513 (Box 11, Folder 17)